# VISHNU DEV M. V.

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**



## **SOFTWARE**

Adobe : Photoshop

Illustrator Indesign After effects Premiere

Blackmagic: DaVinci Resolve



## CONTACT

Mobile: 813 781 5137

E-Mail: vishnu.mv.dev@gmail.com

Location: kochi



## **SKILLS**

Graphic Desgining

Video Editing

Social Media Management



## **HOBBIES**

Watching Anime

Listening Music

Video Game



#### PORTFOLIO





## **ABOUT ME**

My Name is Vishnu Dev, and I'm a graphic designer who believes that design can change the world. With 5 years of experience in the industry, I have had the privilege of working with clients from all walks of life. My specialties include branding, print media, retail brand sales and communications. I'm constantly inspired by the world around me and strive to create designs that are both beautiful and functional.



## **EDUCATION**

M. E. S. COLLEGE Degree

2016 - 2019 B. Voc Animation & Graphic Design

H.I.H.S.S. EDAVANAKKAD 12<sup>th</sup>

2014 - 2015 Humanities

G.V.H.S.S. NARAKKAL 10th

2013 - 2014



# INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer Antz Media, Kathrikadavu, kochi

Oct 2018

VFX Artist IVFX, Kaloor, kochi

Mar 2019

Graphic Designer Sbsol Digital Private Ltd., Kochi

Nov 2019 - Dec 2019



## WORKING EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer Beyond Media Suite, Thrissur

May 2020 - Feb 2022

Graphic Designer Asirvad Micro Finance Ltd., Thrissur

Feb 2022 - Jan 2023

Sr. Graphic Designer Koolath Advertising, kochi

Jan 2023 till date